Boundin' is a animation, family, music film directed by Bud Luckey.
On a high mountain plain lives a lamb with wool of such
remarkable sheen that he breaks into high-steppin' dance.
But there comes a day when he loses his lustrous
coat and, along with it, his pride.
It takes a wise jackalope - a horn-adorned rabbit - to teach the moping lamb that wooly
or not, it's what's inside that'll help him rebound from life's troubles.
Narrator (voice), played by Bud Luckey.
Boundin' is a 2003 American animated short film, which was shown in theaters
before the feature-length superhero film The Incredibles.
The short is a musically narrated story about a dancing lamb,
who loses his confidence after being sheared.
The film was written, directed, narrated and featured the musical
composition and performance of Pixar animator Bud Luckey.
The film explores themes of jumping, lamb, self
esteem, jackalope, sheep shearing.
The tone is lighthearted.